give a sneak preview
I think you in
the medium term so
over the next few
years we believe that
this market could explode
up to 5 trillion
in notional volume Now
right now she is
on an annualized run
rate to do around
120 130 billion in
notional volume for this
year So we're talking
about a massive explosion
of where this total
market is But when
you put it the
perspective of the total
derivatives market which in
2024 was around 715
trillion in notional volume
you're only talking about
70 basis points right
That 5 trillion figure
over 715 So it's
a in the compared
to where traditional derivatives
sit today And as
you point out I
think this is an
expansion of the addressable
market that derivatives don't
necessarily give you today
in terms of the
risk profile